Guide to the John Taber papers, 1880-1965.
Taber, John papers
- Chronological Files, 1938-1960
  - Department of the Navy, 1952 Budget Estimates, Book 1 of 10 Books, 1952 (Box 143)
  - Moravia Bank, 1952-1953 (Box 166)
  - Report of Senate Committee on Appropriation re Interior Department Appropriation Bill, 1952 (Box 130)
  - Report of the Investigative Staff, House committee on Appropriations re Department of Defense 1952 Budget, 1952 (Box 129)
  - Table of Budget Estimates, 1952 (Box 130)
  - Acknowledgements, 1953 (Box 138)
  - Acknowledgements, Gripes, 1953 (Box 100)
  - Agriculture, 1953 (Box 100)
  - Agriculture - Yearbook, 1953 (Box 100)
  - Air Force, 1953 (Box 100)
  - Army, 1953 (Box 100)
  - Cayuga County Republican Committee, 1953 (Box 100)
  - Chenango County Republican Committee, 1953 (Box 100)
  - Civil Aeronautics Administrations, 1953 (Box 100)
  - Civil Service & Employment, 1953 (Box 100)
  - Civil Service & Retirement, 1953 (Box 100)
  - Coast Guard, 1953 (Box 100)
  - Commerce Department, 1953 (Box 100)
  - Condolences, 1953 (Box 100)
  - Congressional Directory, 1953 (Box 100)
  - Congressional Record, 1953 (Box 100)
  - Cornell University, 1953 (Box 100)
  - Federal Communications Commission, 1953 (Box 97)
  - Federal Maritime Board, 1953 (Box 97)
  - Fred J. Douglas (Patronage Case), 1953 (Box 97)
  - General Services Administration, 1953 (Box 97)
  - Health, Education and Welfare, 1953 (Box 147)
  - House Bill 1, 1953 (Box 138)
  - Housing, 1953 (Box 147)
  - Immigration, 1953 (Box 97)
  - Inauguration, 1953 (Box 147)
  - Individual Immigration Cases, 1953 (Box 97)
  - Interior, 1953 (Box 147)
  - John Taber Contributions, 1953 (Box 166)
  - Navy, 1953 (Box 147)
  - Office of the Clerk, 1953 (Box 154)
  - Patronage and Employment Requests, 1953 (Box 97)
  - Receipts - Stationery, Room and Stamps, 1953 (Box 166)
  - Requests for 1953 Yearbook, 1953 (Box 100)
  - Requests for Free Tickets, Passes, etc., 1953 (Box 100)
  - Sampson Air Force Base, 1953 (Box 148)
  - Senate Bills, 1953 (Box 136)
  - Telephone and Telegraphs, 1953 (Box 166)
  - VA Hospital, Syracuse, 1953 (Box 97)
  - Veterans' Claims, 1953 (Box 97)
  - 1954 campaign, 1954 (Box 138)
  - Acknowledgements, 1954 (Box 121)
  - Agriculture, 1954 (Box 121)
  - Agriculture, 1954 (Box 139)
  - Agriculture - Appropriations, 1954 (Box 139)
  - Agriculture Yearbooks, 1954 (Box 121)
  - Air Force, 1954 (Box 121)
  - Air Force (Appropriations), 1954 (Box 136)
  - Appointments, 1954 (Box 121)
  - Appropriations, General, 1954 (Box 166)
  - Armed Services, 1954 (Box 136)
  - Armed Services, 1954 (Box 139)
  - Armed Services Administration, 1954 (Box 121)
  - Army, 1954 (Box 121)
  - Army (Appropriations), 1954 (Box 136)
  - Army, Civil, 1954 (Box 121)
  - Atomic Energy, 1954 (Box 139)
  - Auburn, 1954 (Box 121)
  - Banking and Currency, 1954 (Box 137)
  - Budget, 1954 (Box 136)
  - Buffalo Chamber of Commerce, 1954 (Box 121)
  - Capital, 1954 (Box 121)
  - Capitol Hill Club, 1954 (Box 121)
  - Cayuga County Republican Committee, 1954 (Box 121)
  - Charles Taber, 1954 (Box 166)
  - Chenango County Republican Committee, 1954 (Box 121)
  - Civil Aerunautics Administration, 1954 (Box 121)
  - Civil Service and Retirement, 1954 (Box 121)
  - Civil Service and State Department Blanks, 1954 (Box 121)
  - Clippings, Election, 1954 (Box 122)
  - Coast Guard, 1954 (Box 122)
  - Commerce Department, 1954 (Box 122)
  - Committee on Interstate and Foreign Commerce, 1954 (Box 103)
  - Condolences, 1954 (Box 122)
  - Congressional Directory, 1954 (Box 122)
  - Congressional Record, 1954 (Box 122)
  - Cornell University, 1954 (Box 122)
  - Corps of Engineers, 1954 (Box 122)
  - Cortland County Reppublican Committee, 1954 (Box 122)
  - Defense Department, 1954 (Box 122)
  - Deficiencies, 1954 (Box 138)
  - Department of Interior, 1954 (Box 103)
  - District of Columbia, 1954 (Box 137)
  - District of Columbia, 1954 (Box 138)
  - Elections, 1954 (Box 138)
  - Employment, 1954 (Box 122)
  - Executive Branch of Government, 1954 (Box 122)
  - Federal Communications Commission, 1954 (Box 122)
  - Federal Power Commission, 1954 (Box 122)
  - Federal Spending Facts, 1954, Council of State Chambers of Commerce, 1954 (Box 137)
  - Fish and Wild Life, 1954 (Box 122)
  - Flood Control, 1954 (Box 122)
  - Football tickets, 1954 (Box 122)
  - Foreign Affairs and Aid, 1954 (Box 138)
  - Foreign Operations, 1954 (Box 122)
  - Foreign Operations Administration, 1954 (Box 138)
  - General Accounting Office, 1954 (Box 122)
  - General Services Administration, 1954 (Box 122)
  - Government Operations Committee, 1954 (Box 138)
  - Government Printing Office, 1954 (Box 122)
  - Harry Byrd Committee, 1954 (Box 136)
  - Hawaii and Alaska, 1954 (Box 138)
  - Health, Education and Welfare, 1954 (Box 122)
  - Hoover Commission, 1954 (Box 138)
  - House Bills, 1954 (Box 136)
  - House Judiciary Committee, 1954 (Box 103)
  - Housing, 1954 (Box 122)
  - Housing, 1954 (Box 138)
  - Immigration, 1954 (Box 97)
  - Independent Services, 1954 (Box 136)
  - IndoChina, 1954 (Box 138)
  - Interior Department, 1954 (Box 136)
  - Interior, 1954, 1954 (Box 138)
  - Interstate and Foreign Commerce, 1954 (Box 137)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission, 1954 (Box 103)
  - Investigative Staff, 1954 (Box 137)
  - Invitations, 1954 (Box 103)
  - Invitations, 1954 (Box 122)
  - John Taber, Birthday, 1954 (Box 166)
  - John Taber, Personal, 1954 (Box 166)
  - Judiciary, 1954 (Box 139)
  - Justice and Commerce, 1954 (Box 138)
  - Justice Department, 1954 (Box 103)
  - Labor, 1954 (Box 103)
  - Labor, 1954 (Box 139)
  - Labor and HEW, 1954 (Box 136)
  - Legislative and Judiciary, 1954 (Box 136)
  - Legislative Daily, 1954 (Box 138)
  - Library of Congress, 1954 (Box 103)
  - Miscellaneous Legislation, 1954 (Box 139)
  - National Federation of Independent Business - Ballots, 1954 (Box 139)
  - National Science Foundation, 1954 (Box 139)
  - Navy (Appropriations), 1954 (Box 137)
  - Office of the Clerk, 1954 (Box 136)
  - Passports, 1954 (Box 103)
  - Patronage, 1954 (Box 103)
  - Paul 0. Peters, 1954 (Box 136)
  - Pencil Notes of J. Taber's, 1954 (Box 103)
  - Pending Publications, 1954 (Box 103)
  - Post Office, 1954 (Box 139)
  - Public Opinion, 1954 (Box 103)
  - Public Works, 1954 (Box 139)
  - Publications, 1954 (Box 103)
  - Railroad Retirement, 1954 (Box 103)
  - Reduction of Non-Essential Federal Expenditure, 1954 (Box 139)
  - Republican Members - Appropriations Committee, 1954 (Box 137)
  - Republican National Committee, 1954 (Box 137)
  - Rules Committee, 1954 (Box 139)
  - Selective Service, 1954 (Box 139)
  - Senate Bills, 1954 (Box 136)
  - Small Business Administration, 1954 (Box 97)
  - St. Lawrence Project and Niagara Power Project, 1954 (Box 139)
  - State Department, 1954 (Box 139)
  - State Department (Appropriations), 1954 (Box 139)
  - Statements - Other Members, 1954 (Box 136)
  - Statements, John Taber, 1954 (Box 137)
  - Supplimentals, 1954 (Box 139)
  - Tariff Commission, 1954 (Box 138)
  - Townsend Plan, 1954 (Box 139)
  - U.S. Chamber of Commerce, 1954 (Box 121)
  - U.S.I.A. (Appropriations), 1954 (Box 137)
  - Unamerican Activities, 1954 (Box 138)
  - United Nations, 1954 (Box 138)
  - Universal Military Training, 1954 (Box 138)
  - Veterans Affairs, 1954 (Box 138)
  - Veterans' Claims, 1954 (Box 97)
  - Vote Recanvass, 1954 (Box 138)
  - Ways and Means Committee, 1954 (Box 139)
  - Testimonial Dinner, JT, 1954-01-26 (Box 136)
  - Forty-four identical postcards in support of HB 2344 and S 1685, 1954-04 (Box 139)
  - Letter fron Ithaca Central Labor Union in support of HR 2344, 1954-04-12 (Box 139)
  - Lettor from Norwich Postal Employees in support of HR 2344, 1954-04-22 (Box 139)
  - Thirty identical postcards in support of HR 685 and S 3263, 1954-05-25 (Box 139)
  - Press Release, Small Business Administration, 1954-07-19 (Box 139)
  - Air Force, 1955 (Box 168)
  - Armed Services Information, 1955 (Box 168)
  - Army, 1955 (Box 168)
  - Department of Defense, 1955 (Box 168)
  - Department of Justice, 1955 (Box 104)
  - Department of Labor, 1955 (Box 104)
  - Foreign Operations, 1955-1956 (Box 175)
  - Francis Knight, 1955 (Box 104)
  - Immigration, 1955 (Box 168)
  - Immigration, A - I, 1955 (Box 168)
  - Immigration, J - R, 1955 (Box 168)
  - Immigration, S - Z, 1955 (Box 168)
  - Invitations, 1955 (Box 104)
  - Liaison Offices, 1955 (Box 104)
  - Library of Congress, 1955 (Box 104)
  - Milk Producers, N.Y.S., 1955 (Box 104)
  - Minimum Pay Raise, 1955 (Box 104)
  - Miscellaneous, 1955 (Box 104)
  - Miscellaneous Surveys and Investigations, 1955 (Box 168)
  - Mohawk Airlines, 1955 (Box 104)
  - N.L.R.B., 1955 (Box 104)
  - N.Y.S. Matters, 1955 (Box 104)
  - N.Y.S. Miscellaneous, 1955 (Box 104)
  - N.Y.S. Republican Committee, 1955 (Box 104)
  - National Federation of Independent Voters, 1955 (Box 104)
  - New York Times, 1955 (Box 104)
  - Newsletter, 1955 (Box 104)
  - Newspapers, 1955 (Box 104)
  - Official Register of the U.S., 1955 (Box 163)
  - Passports, 1955 (Box 104)
  - Patronage, 1955 (Box 104)
  - Pending Notes, John Taber, 1955 (Box 104)
  - Poor's Investment Advisory Survey, 1955 (Box 142)
  - Post Office, 1955 (Box 104)
  - Postal News Service, 1955 (Box 104)
  - Postal Pay Raise, 1955 (Box 104)
  - Public Opinion, 1955 (Box 104)
  - Publications, 1955 (Box 104)
  - Radio and Television, 1955 (Box 104)
  - Railroad Retirement, 1955 (Box 104)
  - Reciprocal Trade Agreements, 1955 (Box 104)
  - Recommendations, 1955 (Box 104)
  - Referrals, 1955 (Box 104)
  - Remarks, 1955 (Box 104)
  - Remington Corporation, 1955 (Box 104)
  - Republican Delegation, 1955 (Box 104)
  - Republican Whip, 1955 (Box 104)
  - Robert Zehring Employment Case, 1955-1956 (Box 99)
  - Rural Route Extension Forms, 1955 (Box 104)
  - Soil Survey, Ontario and Yates Counties, N.Y., 1955 (Box 168)
  - The Federal Budget in Brief, 1955 (Box 168)
  - Veterans, 1955 (Box 168)
  - Veterans Administrative, A - I, 1955 (Box 168)
  - Veterans Administrative, J - R, 1955 (Box 168)
  - Veterans Administrative, S - Z, 1955 (Box 168)
  - Veterans, General, 1955 (Box 168)
  - Braver Case, 1956 (Box 98)
  - Hawaiian Ports, 1956 (Box 98)
  - HR 12080, Public Works, 1956 (Box 98)
  - Independent Offices, 1956 (Box 98)
  - Interior Department, 1956 (Box 98)
  - Investigative Reports, 1956 (Box 98)
  - McGlade Case, 1956 (Box 98)
  - Military and Financial Aid to the Far-East, 1956 (Box 99)
  - Military Construction Data, 1956 (Box 98)
  - N.Y. Flood Control, 1956 (Box 99)
  - Public Works, 1956 (Box 99)
  - Public Works Information and Logrolling Correspondence, 1956 (Box 98)
  - RIAS (vs. Radio Station in Berlin), 1956 (Box 99)
  - State and Justice Department Appropriations Bill, 1956 (Box 99)
  - Supplemental Appropriations Bills, 1956 (Box 99)
  - Treasury and Post Office Departments, 1956 (Box 99)
  - TVA, 1956 (Box 99)
  - Urgent Deficiency, 1956 (Box 175)
  - Appropriations, 1957 (Box 170)
  - Appropriations - General, 1957 (Box 170)
  - Appropriations, Investigative Reports, 1957 (Box 170)
  - Byrd Committee, 1957 (Box 170)
  - Colonial Division - Eastern Airlines, 1957 (Box 172)
  - Commerce Department, 1957 (Box 170)
  - Defense Department, 1957 (Box 170)
  - Deficiency, Post Office Department, 1957 (Box 170)
  - Department of Agriculture, 1957 (Box 170)
  - District of Columbia Sub-Committee, 1957 (Box 170)
  - Federal Budget (Corres. w/ constituents, 1957 (Box 170)
  - Federal Budget (corresp. w/ constituents, 1957 (Box 172)
  - Foreign Aid, 1957 (Box 170)
  - Independent Offices, 1957 (Box 170)
  - Interior Department, 1957 (Box 170)
  - Labor, Health, Education and Welfare, 1957 (Box 170)
  - Mohawk Airlines - Erie, Detroit Service, 1957 (Box 172)
  - Mr. Taber, 1957 (Box 170)
  - Ontario and Western Railroads, 1957 (Box 172)
  - Proposed Changes in Route 11, 1957 (Box 172)
  - Public Works, 1957 (Box 172)
  - Representative Congressional Committee, 1957 (Box 172)
  - White House, 1957 (Box 172)
  - 1958 Yearbook, N.Y. Republican State Committee, 1958 (Box 163)
  - Accrued Expenditure, 1958 (Box 2)
  - Acknowledgements, 1958 (Box 124)
  - Agriculture, 1958 (Box 2)
  - Annual Report of the Smithsonian Institution, 1958 (Box 163)
  - Appropriations, 1958 (Box 124)
  - Banking and Currency, 1958 (Box 2)
  - Civil Rights, 1958 (Box 2)
  - Civil Service and Post Office, 1958 (Box 2)
  - Civil Servive and Post Office, 1958 (Box 2)
  - Congressional Committee, 1958 (Box 2)
  - History of the U.S. House of Representatives, 1958-1959 (Box 163)
  - Rockefeller Foundation Annual Report, 1958 (Box 163)
  - The Biographic Register, 1958 (Box 163)
  - Washington Office, 1958 (Box 124)
  - Acknowledgements (several folders), 1959 (Box 1)
  - Agricultural Departments, 1959 (Box 1)
  - Agricultural Facts, 1959 (Box 1)
  - Agriculture Year Books, 1959 (Box 1)
  - Applications for employment, 1959 (Box 1)
  - Appointments, 1959 (Box 1)
  - Appropriations, General, 1959 (Box 171)
  - Appropriations, The Budget, 1959 (Box 171)
  - Army & Tickets, 1959 (Box 1)
  - Atomic Energy Commission, 1959 (Box 1)
  - Auburn, 1959 (Box 1)
  - Buffalo Chamber of Commerce, 1959 (Box 1)
  - Bureau of Budget, 1959 (Box 1)
  - Bureau of Budget [Bureau of Census], 1959 (Box 1)
  - Capitol, 1959 (Box 1)
  - Central Intelligence Agency, 1959 (Box 1)
  - Chiropractic Association, 1959 (Box 1)
  - Civil Aeronautics, 1959 (Box 1)
  - Civil Defense, 1959 (Box 1)
  - Civil Service Employment, 1959 (Box 1)
  - Civil Service General, 1959 (Box 1)
  - Civil Service Retirement, 1959 (Box 1)
  - Clippings, 1959 (Box 1)
  - Commerce Department, 1959 (Box 1)
  - Condolences, 1959 (Box 1)
  - Congressional Dictionary, 1959 (Box 1)
  - Congressional Record, 1959 (Box 1)
  - Cornell University, 1959 (Box 1)
  - Corps of Engineers, 1959 (Box 1)
  - Department of Defense Appropriation Bill, 1959 (Box 163)
  - Diary, 1959 (Box 1)
  - Few miscellaneous papers, 1959 (Box 171)
  - Ford Foundation Annual Report, 1959 (Box 163)
  - House Bills - 86th - First, 1959 (Box 171)
  - House Bills, 86th Congress, First, 1959 (Box 176)
  - House Floor, 1959 (Box 176)
  - House Resolution 161, 1959 (Box 176)
  - Independent Offices Appropriation Bill, 1959 (Box 163)
  - Labor - H.E.W. Appropriations, 1959 (Box 163)
  - Legis. Agriculture, 1959 (Box 171)
  - Legis. Alcoholic, 1959 (Box 171)
  - Legis. Armed Services, 1959 (Box 171)
  - Legis. Banking and Currency, 1959 (Box 171)
  - Legis. District of Columbia, 1959 (Box 171)
  - Legis. Education and Labor, 1959 (Box 171)
  - Legis. Housing, 1959 (Box 171)
  - Legis. Immigration, 1959 (Box 176)
  - Legis. Int. and Ins. Affairs, 1959 (Box 171)
  - Legis. Interstate and Foreign Commerce, 1959 (Box 176)
  - Legis. Judiciary, 1959 (Box 176)
  - Legis. P.O. and C.S., 1959 (Box 176)
  - Legis. Public Works, 1959 (Box 176)
  - Legis. School Bill, 1959 (Box 176)
  - Legis. Social Security, 1959 (Box 176)
  - Legis. Space, 1959 (Box 176)
  - Legis. Taxes and Tariffs, 1959 (Box 176)
  - Legis. Unamerican Activities, 1959 (Box 176)
  - Legis. Veterans Affairs, 1959 (Box 176)
  - Legis. Ways and Means, 1959 (Box 176)
  - Legislative - Highway bill, 1959 (Box 171)
  - Legislative - private bills, 1959 (Box 171)
  - Legislative Miscellaneous, 1959 (Box 176)
  - Legislative, Miscellaneous, 1959 (Box 167)
  - Legislative, Miscellaneous, 1959 (Box 167)
  - Office of the Clerk, 1959 (Box 171)
  - Public Works Appropriation Bill, 1959 (Box 163)
  - Representatives - Congressional Committee, 1959 (Box 171)
  - Representatives - National Committee, 1959 (Box 171)
  - Representatives - policy committee, 1959 (Box 171)
  - Republican Congressional Committee, 1959 (Box 167)
  - Republican National Committee, 1959 (Box 171)
  - Senate Bills, 86th Congress, First, 1959 (Box 176)
  - Statements, 1959 (Box 176)
  - The World Almanac and Book of Facts, 1959 (Box 163)
  - Voting Record, 1959 (Box 171)
  - White House, 1959 (Box 167)
  - Three Pamphlets, 1960 (Box 170)
  - 1st Deficiency, Date Unknown (Box 126)
  - Agriculture, Date Unknown (Box 124)
  - Agriculture, Date Unknown (Box 126)
  - Agriculture Year Book, Date Unknown (Box 119)
  - Agriculture Year Books, prior years, Date Unknown (Box 1)
  - Air Force, Date Unknown (Box 119)
  - Appointments, Date Unknown (Box 119)
  - Appointments, Date Unknown (Box 124)
  - Appropriations - Public Works, McGee Bend Dam, Date Unknown (Box 166)
  - Appropriations - Punch Card Equipment Government Agencies, Date Unknown (Box 139)
  - Appropriations Bills, 83rd Congress, Second Session, Date Unknown (Box 137)
  - Appropriations, Miscellaneous, Date Unknown (Box 124)
  - Army, Date Unknown (Box 119)
  - Army, Civil, Date Unknown (Box 119)
  - Army-Navy Football Tickets, Date Unknown (Box 97)
  - Benton, William, Date Unknown (Box 166)
  - Bob Lee, Date Unknown (Box 138)
  - Bureau of Budget, Date Unknown (Box 116)
  - Cassidy, James E., Date Unknown (Box 166)
  - Chamber of Commerce, Date Unknown (Box 124)
  - Charles Heiser, Date Unknown (Box 147)
  - Check Off List for Weekly Review of ECA Progress, Date Unknown (Box 129)
  - Clippings, Date Unknown (Box 124)
  - Colonial Air Lines, Date Unknown (Box 143)
  - Columbian Rope Company, Date Unknown (Box 143)
  - Commentary re Statements, J.T., Date Unknown (Box 154)
  - Committee for Congested Areas, Date Unknown (Box 126)
  - Comptroller - General, Date Unknown (Box 116)
  - Condolences, Date Unknown (Box 124)
  - Cord and Rope Industry, Date Unknown (Box 143)
  - Corps of Engineers Report on Rivers and Harbors, Date Unknown (Box 130)
  - Cross reference file, Date Unknown (Box 124)
  - Currier - From Sub-committee, Date Unknown (Box 136)
  - Deering, James R., Date Unknown (Box 166)
  - Deficiencies, Date Unknown (Box 126)
  - Deficiency Material, Date Unknown (Box 126)
  - District of Columbia, Date Unknown (Box 126)
  - Dresser, R. B. (Edwards and Angell, Providence, R.I.), Date Unknown (Box 166)
  - E - H, Date Unknown (Box 148)
  - Economic Cooperation Administration, Date Unknown (Box 115)
  - Economic Cooperation Administration - Mining Machinery, Date Unknown (Box 115)
  - Economic Stabilization Agency, Date Unknown (Box 97)
  - Employment, Date Unknown (Box 97)
  - Envelope containing four pamphlets, Date Unknown (Box 163)
  - Estimates on Appropriations, Date Unknown (Box 126)
  - European Assistance Plans, Date Unknown (Box 128)
  - European Trip, Date Unknown (Box 142)
  - Farm Labor, Date Unknown (Box 126)
  - Farm Labor, Date Unknown (Box 126)
  - Federal Works Agency, Date Unknown (Box 116)
  - Financing the Marshall Plan Through International Cooperation, Date Unknown (Box 130)
  - Fish and Wildlife Service, Date Unknown (Box 97)
  - Football tickets, Date Unknown (Box 124)
  - Four Absentee Ballot Applications, Date Unknown (Box 130)
  - Frances, Date Unknown (Box 136)
  - General Accounting Office, Date Unknown (Box 97)
  - General Appropriation Bill, Conference Report, Date Unknown (Box 129)
  - Government Corporation, Date Unknown (Box 116)
  - Guide to the Palace of Westminster, Date Unknown (Box 129)
  - Harold Blake, Date Unknown (Box 166)
  - HEW and Related Agencies, Date Unknown (Box 98)
  - Home Loan Bank Board (Hearing before J. Aldrich Hall), Date Unknown (Box 166)
  - Hoover, Herbert, Date Unknown (Box 166)
  - House Bills, 83rd Congress, Second Session, Date Unknown (Box 136)
  - HR 5604, Second Recession, Date Unknown (Box 129)
  - HR 588, Aid Bill to Austria, China, and France and Italy, Date Unknown (Box 129)
  - HUAC Correspondence, Date Unknown (Box 98)
  - I - N, Date Unknown (Box 148)
  - Independent Offices, Date Unknown (Box 126)
  - Individual Immigration Cases, Date Unknown (Box 140)
  - Institute of Pacific Relations, Date Unknown (Box 116)
  - Interior, Date Unknown (Box 115)
  - Interior, Date Unknown (Box 126)
  - Internal Revenue, Date Unknown (Box 124)
  - Interstate and Foreign Commerce, Date Unknown (Box 147)
  - Invitations, Date Unknown (Box 124)
  - Invitations, Date Unknown (Box 147)
  - Jameson, Guildford S., Date Unknown (Box 166)
  - John Taber Receipts, Date Unknown (Box 166)
  - John Taber Receipts, Date Unknown (Box 166)
  - John Taber, Clippings, Date Unknown (Box 154)
  - JT Statement Calling for Increased Military Effort and Sacrifice by Civilian Population, Date Unknown (Box 130)
  - JT's Notebook on Joint Committee on Foreign Economic Cooperation, Date Unknown (Box 129)
  - JT's Pencil Notes from Briefing on Post-war European Economic, Administrative, and Military Situation, Date Unknown (Box 128)
  - Judiciary, Date Unknown (Box 126)
  - Judiciary, Date Unknown (Box 147)
  - Justice, Date Unknown (Box 147)
  - Kaiser - Frazer Corporation, Date Unknown (Box 116)
  - Korea, Date Unknown (Box 143)
  - Labor, Date Unknown (Box 147)
  - Labor - Federal Security, Date Unknown (Box 126)
  - Labor and Federal Security, Date Unknown (Box 115)
  - Labor Reform Bills, Date Unknown (Box 167)
  - Legislative - Judiciary, Date Unknown (Box 126)
  - Legislative Labor Reform Bill, Date Unknown (Box 167)
  - Lend-Lease Appropriations, Date Unknown (Box 126)
  - Letters of Recommendation, Date Unknown (Box 147)
  - Letters of Recommendations, Date Unknown (Box 103)
  - Letters of Recommendations, Date Unknown (Box 123)
  - Library of Congress, Date Unknown (Box 147)
  - M. S. Burnside Case, Date Unknown (Box 97)
  - Mailing List for statements of John Taber, Date Unknown (Box 136)
  - Man, Soil and Conservation, Date Unknown (Box 130)
  - Maplegrove Apartments, Date Unknown (Box 124)
  - Marine Corps, Date Unknown (Box 103)
  - Marine Corps, Date Unknown (Box 147)
  - Marshall Plan, Date Unknown (Box 115)
  - Martino, Nick, Date Unknown (Box 166)
  - Memos, Date Unknown (Box 103)
  - Memos re U.N.R.R.A. Shipping Quantities and Expenses, Date Unknown (Box 129)
  - Military Affairs, Date Unknown (Box 142)
  - Military Appropriations and Investigations, Date Unknown (Box 142)
  - Milk Marketing, Date Unknown (Box 124)
  - Minority Reports - Bob Lee, Date Unknown (Box 166)
  - Miscellaneous, Date Unknown (Box 103)
  - Miscellaneous, Date Unknown (Box 124)
  - Miscellaneous, Date Unknown (Box 143)
  - Miscellaneous - Subject, Date Unknown (Box 147)
  - Miscellaneous Acts and Bills, Date Unknown (Box 167)
  - Miscellaneous Appropriations, Date Unknown (Box 141)
  - Miscellaneous Clippings, and Statements, Date Unknown (Box 142)
  - Miscellaneous Letters, Memos, Etc., Date Unknown (Box 141)
  - Mr. Taber, Date Unknown (Box 124)
  - Mrs. Murray Brophy, Date Unknown (Box 166)
  - Munitions Building, Date Unknown (Box 147)
  - Mutual Security Program (Unclassified), Date Unknown (Box 167)
  - N.Y.S. Canners, Date Unknown (Box 126)
  - National Production Authority, Date Unknown (Box 147)
  - National Small Businessmen's Association, Date Unknown (Box 154)
  - Navy, Date Unknown (Box 103)
  - Navy, Date Unknown (Box 126)
  - New York Republican Delegation, Date Unknown (Box 147)
  - New York State Commerce Review, Date Unknown (Box 137)
  - New York State Matters, Date Unknown (Box 103)
  - New York State Matters, Date Unknown (Box 147)
  - Newsletters, Date Unknown (Box 103)
  - Newsletters, Date Unknown (Box 124)
  - Newspaper Clippings, General John C. H. Lee, Date Unknown (Box 142)
  - Newspaper, 36th District, Date Unknown (Box 103)
  - Newspapers - 36th District, Date Unknown (Box 147)
  - O - S, Date Unknown (Box 148)
  - Office Chief of Counsel For War Crimes, U.S. Army - Data on Personnel, Date Unknown (Box 128)
  - Office of Education, Date Unknown (Box 97)
  - Office of Education, Date Unknown (Box 97)
  - Office of Price Administration, Date Unknown (Box 116)
  - Ontario County Republican Committee, Date Unknown (Box 103)
  - Ontario County Republican Committee, Date Unknown (Box 147)
  - Organization Manual of the Department of the Navy, Date Unknown (Box 142)